A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1974-1975
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- University Center in Virginia 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- University Editor 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- University Police 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- University Press of Virginia 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- University Register 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- University Relations--General 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- University Relations--Information Services 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- University Relations--Medical Center Information 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- University Relations--Radio and TV 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- University Research Policy Council 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- University Union 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- Upward Bound Program 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- Urban Observatory Program 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- "V" Miscellaneous 1974-1975 (Box 25)
- Virginia Commission on Higher Education Facilities 1974-1975 (Box 26)
- Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1974-1975 (Box 26)
- Virginia Quarterly Review 1974-1975 (Box 26)
- "W-Wh" Miscellaneous--Article: "FDR as a Prophet" by W. Allen Wallie, Memoirs of Linwood H. Warwick-Part I & II 1974-1975 (Box 26)
- "Wi-Wz" Miscellaneous 1974-1975 (Box 26)
  Article from Journal of Legal Education, Kuhlman-Wilsdorf's Progress Report on Investigation on the Behavior of Point Defects and Dislocations
- "X-Y-Z" Miscellaneous--Pamphlet of Mento-Factor System (Xerox), Closing of the Zeta Beta Tau Fraternity 1974-1975 (Box 26)